ALL NAMES, CHARACTERS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD AND ANIMAL WELFARE
REGULATIONS WERE OBSERVED
You're with Hwa-jin, right?
Bring her over right now.
I'll take her
to President-elect
and have it out with him.
But Lee Hwa-jin is
with President-elect's daughter now.
What?
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Let me
meet that person.
Who?
Lee Hwa-jin.
I read it because you asked me to.
But why?
I thought you might be curious
about why my mom did that.
I would've been curious
if I were in your shoes.
Basically, she had a reason
she couldn't turn herself in.
It was all for Mr. Hyun.
Mr. Hyun?
I mean Dad.
I called her dad "Mr. Hyun."
But I don't know.
That was really just an accident?
It was a coincidence?
And you want me
to believe that?
What do you mean?
Are you suspecting
that she caused the accident
on purpose?
Why not?
Can't I have suspicions?
When you suspect others as you like?
What?
You suspected that
Mr. Hyun and I were having an affair.
Wasn't that why Ms. Cha suspected me too?
I'm leaving.
Weren't you the one who asked to meet me?
You still act like a princess.
You said to me last time
that you wanted to live an ordinary life.
That you wanted to live
with ordinary parents.
You wanted to quit
being the presidential candidate's
and president's daughter whatnot.
When you said that,
do you know what went through my mind?
"She's so ungrateful."
Whenever you blabbered about how tough
things were, do you know what I thought?
"She's so spoiled and immature."
Some people
don't even get to have someone
who can spoil them.
Even now,
my mom is dead,
and you're here acting like a baby.
Ji-yu.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to apologize to you
in person in my mom's stead.
I don't know if an apology will cut it.
I don't deserve to receive an apology.
That's not it.
I'm not asking for forgiveness.
The same goes for that.
It's not up to me to forgive.
Hyun Ji-yu.
It's nice to see you here.
Where are you going? You're leaving?
Aren't you glad to see us again?
She's the president's daughter.
I can't believe we met here.
I still owe you something.
Shall we shoot the sequel?
We definitely should.
Let's stream it live.
We'll make use
of the celebrity to get high views.
Don't.
Don't do what?
You're so shameless.
Hey.
I'm suspended from school because you.
This is the least you can do.
Don't you agree?
Of course.
You should pay for what you did.
Gang-myeong. An Gang-myeong!
What're you doing? Get her!
Hurry up!
HYUN JI-YU
Sit here.
No, it's okay.
Seeing you stand
makes me feel uncomfortable.
Okay, then.
Hold on to me.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
You're very adept at it,
like a professional caregiver.
My husband had
a long rehabilitation period.
When I first met you,
I thought you were very much like him.
Now that you're in this state,
you look even more like him.
Do I?
I don't see the resemblance.
He was angry too, just like you.
He wanted to take revenge
on the company for Tae-hun,
who was denied worker's compensation.
Just like how you wanted
to take revenge on me.
Don't look at me like that.
It was the same for me.
I also wanted to take revenge
on my father.
I wanted to take revenge on Father,
who drove Mom to an early grave
to become an assemblyman.
It's always anger that drives people.
I realized that too young.
So I was going to use your anger
and your desire for revenge.
But
there's something I didn't know.
Anger
blinds you.
And the first thing
the blinded anger goes after
is none other than myself.
I realized that too late.
Losing someone precious to you.
I guess I was too young to know
what it felt like
when my mom had died.
But
now that I could lose Ms. Sung,
I can finally understand.
I'm sorry.
I knew from the start
that you lost your parents
to the fire.
I knew you were the family of the victims,
but I tried to use you.
You're sorry?
Do you remember Song In-gyeong?
You wouldn't.
What about Kang In-gyu?
Are they your late parents?
You must've met them.
Fifteen years ago,
when there was the fire,
you were there too.
Did you see why and how
my parents had died that day?
Do you remember?
At first, I doubted and hated Do Tae-hun.
I believed what the media said
and thought he'd killed my parents.
But
Uncle Ki-ju told me.
It was someone else
who killed my parents.
Who
is that?
killed my parents?
Was it you, Ms. Cha?
Was it
really you?
The person standing on the receiving end
isn't Yang Hoon.
It's Su-yeon.
I just want to know the last moments
of my parents.
Honey.
I'm sorry,
but I need to talk to my wife.
I met the first lady.
She said you were behind the fire.
That you staged it with Yang Hoon
so I could win the election.
Is it true?
Did you really do it?
I did it.
I killed them.
You…
It's true.
Honey!
Is that true?
Was it really your doing?
To win the election?
It was all planned?
I could become an assemblyman…
and the president…
because they lost their lives.
Tae-hun.
In-gyu.
And In-gyeong. Their lost lives.
When the doctor said
you wouldn't be able to stand
and walk again,
do you know what went through my mind?
I thought about how strong a weapon
it would be for your political career.
Don't make that face.
Had you become
permanently wheelchair-bound,
you would've become the president
five years ago, not now.
I didn't love you.
I just needed someone
to become the president.
To drag down Cha Jeong-yeon
and take revenge on my father.
I used you.
I'm sorry.
I need some time to think.
But the security rule says…
Please.
This will be my last request.
Then we'll wait here.
Will you be okay on your own?
You kept making a fuss
saying you were okay,
so I left.
But leaving a patient to himself
makes me feel uneasy.
Grandma, I'm not a patient.
I'll be discharged in two days,
so just focus on your work.
Don't leave your regular customers
to starve.
Fine, then. Take good care of yourself.
Make sure you eat the beef bone soup.
I'm making more, so eat up.
Beef bone soup is best to heal your bones.
I'll visit tomorrow.
Oh, Grandma.
Do you have something to say?
It's nothing.
I wanted to say something,
but I forgot.
You silly.
I'm hanging up.
Take good care of yourself.
That's rare
for a car to drive all the way there.
Ms. Sung.
What should I do now?
Why won't you say anything?
You said you'd believe me,
no matter what I did.
You said you'd be on my side.
Why won't you say anything?
Ms. Sung.
Hello, Ji-yu.
Ms. Cha Su-yeon, listen carefully.
Who is this?
Why are you on Ji-yu's…
Ji-yu is with me.
Who are you?
If you want to meet Ji-yu,
come over with the voice recorder.
Yang Hoon?
Is it Yang Hoon?
Driver Kim is there, right?
Hand your phone over to him
and follow him with the recorder.
Driver Kim.
This isn't what I think it is, right?
Let me speak with Ji-yu.
I need to make sure Ji-yu is safe first.
Put Ji-yu on the phone now!
Mom!
Ji-yu, are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
I'll be there soon.
I'll be there soon, so hang in there.
Okay?
Do as I say, and you can meet Ji-yu.
I'll do as you say.
So don't lay a finger on Ji-yu.
If something happens to her,
I'll kill you.
Stay still.
Why turn it off--
You have the recorder, don't you?
This way.
My gosh!
Wait for a while.
I'll go to the Special Committee
and reveal the truth.
The earlier, the better.
See you at the Committee meeting
three days later.
Thank you.
Why are you here alone?
Your bodyguards?
What about them?
They always accompanied you.
They need a break too.
But what do you mean that you'll go
to the Special Committee yourself?
I'm sorry.
Please wait for a few days.
What I said
at the charnel house last time.
Forget that.
Sun-jeong suddenly passed away,
and I found out she had a daughter.
Too many things happened at once,
so I couldn't
be considerate of your feelings.
I'm sure you were upset too.
I was grateful.
What?
You scolded me
like I was still your son.
I was…
grateful and glad for it.
You feel glad for anything and everything.
Scold me as much as you like.
Reprimand me as much as you like.
I've more things left for you to scold.
You should scold me
so that making Tae-hun die…
Because of me, Tae-hun…
The noodles will get soggy. Eat up.
I won't disturb you. Start eating.
What's happening?
The neighborhood thugs
or shady-looking kids
would come occasionally,
but cars are driving in
one after another today.
WIFE
The person you called is unavailable.
Ji-yu!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt anywhere?
Mom, I'm sorry.
Why would you be sorry? I'm sorry.
Are you hurt anywhere?
No.
Goodness.
This is my favorite scene.
I almost missed it.
What do you want?
Goal.
Let Ji-yu go.
Then I'll keep
my mouth shut forever as you wish.
You're the evidence.
I should get rid of it.
I can't live worrying about it forever.
The historic moment from 15 years ago
that dominated the news
will hit the headlines again.
I'll do whatever you say.
Just spare Ji-yu.
Let, let Ji-yu go.
Mom!
This has nothing to do with her!
It had nothing to do with the old woman
who got in the accident.
Please, I beg you.
Yang Hoon, please just spare Ji-yu.
Let her go!
Darn it.
Are you serious?
I respected you so much,
and you're begging me
just to spare your kid?
Just spare Ji-yu, Yang Hoon.
I beg you. Spare her, Yang Hoon!
Are you going to burn the place down?
Do you think you can get away with this?
Fire?
That won't work.
Firefighters arrive very quickly nowadays.
Everyone thinks fire itself kills people,
but the one that's really dangerous
is toxic gas.
I'm the CEO
of a chemical plant, you see.
This is
phosgene.
And it's very dangerous.
No.
Mr. Jung, finish this.
-Yes, sir.
-Yang Hoon!
Yang Hoon!
They say fire is the best sight to watch.
It's nothing much.
Yang Hoon.
Gosh, you startled me.
I'm sorry.
Repent all you want in there.
Have fun with your daughter.
At least the mom and the daughter
will be together until the end.
That makes me feel relieved.
Just let Ji-yu go.
Please let her go!
Yang Hoon!
Yang Hoon, open the door!
Open the door!
Let Ji-yu go!
Yang Hoon, let Ji-yu go!
Mom, I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Shush, don't say anything.
You can't breathe in the gas.
There's someone here!
Save me.
Mom.
-Did you hear that too?
-Yes.
There's someone here.
Save me.
Honey!
Ji-yu.
Ji-yu!
Ji-yu. Hyun Ji-yu.
Ji-yu.
Dad.
Dad is here.
I'm here, so don't worry.
You'll be fine soon.
Where's Mom?
Mom…
Can you go alone?
No, don't go.
I'll take her and get out soon.
It's dangerous here. Wait outside.
You'll go back in there
when you don't even know who she is?
You can't.
What would Dad have done?
If Dad were here,
he'd never give up on saving someone.
Mom.
I'll be back soon.
She was with me until just now.
She went back in to save someone.
I'll go get her. Wait here.
Lee Hwa-jin?
What should I do?
If there's a victim,
there should be a perpetrator.
She killed Cha Su-yeon and her daughter
to avenge her mom
and died herself too.
It's neat.
Yes, sir.
Text a will
to her friend
and get rid of them all here.
Lee Hwa-jin!
Ms. Cha.
Don't worry.
We can go out.
Lee Hwa-jin.
Hwa-jin!
I'll do it.
Honey.
Stand back. I'll open it quickly.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
What about Ji-yu?
Ji-yu is fine too.
Let's go.
Wait.
Hwa-jin.
Hwa-jin?
She passed out.
Here.
-Hwa-jin.
-Lee Hwa-jin.
Hwa-jin.
Watch out!
Lee Hwa-jin.
Hwa-jin.
Can you hear me?
Honey.
Give me a second.
I'll get you out soon.
Honey.
I'm sorry. Because of me, Yang Hoon…
Don't be sorry.
I should've known
why you did that.
I should've known.
I'm sorry.
No.
You did nothing wrong. Don't say that.
Do you still not get it?
My biggest fault
is that I didn't know.
I of all people should've known
what you did and why you did it.
What my loved one did and why.
I should've known.
Honey.
The building is cracking.
It could collapse at any time. So…
take Hwa-jin and leave.
No.
I won't.
Take the girl and leave.
I don't want to.
Now. There's no time.
No!
-I won't!
-There's no time. Go now!
No, I won't!
Just wait. I can do this!
-Honey.
-No.
Think about Ji-yu.
No, honey. Don't do this.
No.
Don't do this.
Go out with her. Don't give up.
I can't leave without you.
No, don't do this.
Please don't do this to me.
-No.
-I'll leave it to you.
-Go now!
Ji-yu is waiting. Get out now.
Honey, hang in there. I'll be back soon.
Just hang in there for a bit.
Okay? I'll be back soon.
Get up. Let's go.
Stand up.
-Dad.
-Stand up now.
Dad.
You have a photo, right?
Goodness.
Your daughter looks just like your wife.
Don't be too disappointed, though.
Now that I take a closer look,
she has your eyes.
You worked hard.
Do you know how rough it was?
I really had a hard time.
I know.
I really--
You did…
a great job.
I'm sorry.
You're awake.
Why're you sleeping like this?
I came home late.
I was going to rest for five minutes.
But I was too tired and fell asleep.
You must be very tired.
Sleep comfortably on the bed.
Just five minutes.
Let's stay like this for five.
You have an appointment at dawn.
Get up now.
Then one minute.
What is it?
Why look at me that way?
Is something on my face?
Honey.
Are you really here?
It's the shortest minute in the world.
Ms. Cha?
Where's my husband?
Yang was arrested warrantless
for setting the old factory on fire.
I don't know anything. It wasn't me!
Yang denied his charge,
but Jung and Kim who were arrested
for setting the fire
as per Yang's orders admitted their crime.
They kidnapped President-elect's daughter,
lured Ms. Cha to the factory,
and tried to kill them
by starting the fire.
The police secured
evidence that Yang was involved in
the car accident a few days ago
and are interrogating him.
Ms. Cha and her daughter
were rescued safely,
but President-elect,
who saved his family from the fire,
went missing.
The search authorities are
continuing the search for two days,
but some are expressing their concerns
that the golden hour has already passed.
-Dad.
-Stand up now.
Dad.
Ms. Sung
wanted to talk to you about your mom.
About my mom?
I'm sorry.
What?
Why're you suddenly apologizing?
On the day of the accident,
I chased
after your mom.
You chased after my mom?
To see her daughter…
To see her daughter even from a distance,
she came by for the whole week,
and I spotted her.
But
she ran away when I recognized her.
Mom came
to see me?
I'm sure of it.
This old woman here
got too scared.
I ended up running away.
I'm sorry.
TESTIMONY BY SHIN HAE-RIN
What about President-elect?
He's still missing?
The unprecedented situation
of President-elect being missing
made the politicians dumbfounded.
Both the Participation People's party
and Party for Peace and Freedom
are wishing for his safe return.
The Presidential Transition Committee
hasn't announced their stance,
except that they're sticking to
their transitioning duties.
Hello?
How's the Committee?
Secretary Shin.
I heard Ms. Cha was attending it.
Yes.
She'll attend on the day
Mr. Hyun was supposed to.
She has something to say about the fire.
Minister nominations?
The inauguration is around the corner.
President-elect has high standards.
You must check thoroughly.
Don't worry.
I'm handling all the tasks
you used to work on.
President-elect
doesn't accept sloppy work.
I'm working like there's no weekends.
I'm losing so much weight.
I thought you could wear one of these
to go to the Committee.
Since the occasion is such…
He…
is alive.
I apologize.
Ms. Cha attended
the Special Committee meeting
this afternoon in President-elect's stead.
Ms. Cha was accused of being involved
with Chairman Yang Hoon of H Chemical.
People are wondering
if she'll reveal the truth.
The contract workers
and the police who forced their way
into the factory to drag out
the sit-in protesters
caused the fire 15 years ago.
Do Tae-hun and other union members
were innocent victims.
So are the six people
who were at the scene of the fire,
including Song In-gyeong
and Kang In-gyu.
They died wrongful deaths.
And they're innocent.
If what you're saying is true,
you yourself
won't be free from the responsibility.
I already made the same statement
to the police.
I won't hide
or run anymore.
I'll take responsibility.
I'll accept the punishment too.
But
Yang Hoon and the contractors
aren't the only criminals.
Late Cha Jin-taek
of Party for Peace and Freedom
framed innocent Do Tae-hun
to be the perpetrator.
So did President Yu Jin-myeong.
The person who leaked the fabricated
investigation result to the media and
is present here
as the special committee member.
Noh Cheol-jae, the prosecutor back then.
Witness!
Do you have proof?
Remember the oath you took!
You'll be punished for perjury
if you give a false statement.
I have the transaction history between
him and Yang Hoon,
plus the recordings of our phone calls.
If it's evidence you want,
I can give it to you right now.
Mr. Noh.
Take your seat.
This time is for the witness.
Lastly, the media
that influenced the public
by reporting
the fabricated investigation result
as if it's true
without checking the facts.
All of them
must be responsible.
I understand.
The Special Committee
will investigate that too.
Thank you for testifying for a long time.
Is there anything else you want to say?
I'll give you time.
My husband said
to change the world,
he himself should change first.
To change the world,
you must change yourself first.
By changing one person like that,
you change the world.
By saving one person like that,
you save the world.
Because
each and every person
is the world.
Changing and saving the world.
He didn't do politics
with such grandiose hope.
My husband did politics
because he was afraid that the world
would change him.
He was afraid he'd turn a blind eye
to the injured,
that he'd turn his back on the coworker
who's fighting alone,
and that he'd use his family and daughter
as excuses to sacrifice someone
and become happy on his own.
I knew from the beginning
that he didn't give up on anyone,
not a single person.
That's why
I loved him.
My father
sacrificed my mom
to become an assemblyman.
My husband wouldn't let
anyone sacrifice themselves,
even if that meant
he'd become the president.
That's why
I married him.
I don't know
if my husband saved the world.
But he did save
a person's life.
He saved me.
I don't know if my husband
changed the world.
But he changed me.
It's my turn now.
It's my turn to save him.
To me, he is…
My whole world.
He will
definitely
come back.
Ms. Sung made this for you.
She's a patient herself.
She shouldn't have.
Is he the baby's dad?
I really can't get used to it.
That he's the baby's dad
and I am
a mom.
When Ji-yu was young,
she loved a tricycle.
She'd always say that we three as a family
were like a tricycle.
You, him, and the baby
are now a tricycle too.
Get used to it soon.
Are we?
It's cold and windy. You should go back.
Then
wear this at least.
It looks good on you.
Here! He's here!
Over here!
Secure airway, check for injuries!
Check for breathing!